[loud drum plays]
[ominous choral music creeping in]
[tense music]
[footsteps thudding]
[intense choral music]
[choral music intensifies]
[growls]
[snarls]
[choral music continues]
[footsteps thudding]
[intense choral music]
[rumbling]
[crows cawing]
[brooding music]
[Hera] Giants of the deep, hear me.
[snarls]
[growls]
[rumbling]
[crackles]
[whooshes]
[growls]
[groans]
[splashes]
[hisses]
I thought you'd see it my way.
[low growl]
[Hera] Help me kill Zeus…
and I'll make the sea yours again.
[thunder rumbling]
[retches]
[pants]
No.
[thunder rumbling]
[crackling]
[groans]
[breathing deeply]
[thunder rumbling]
[epic music]
[intense choral music]
Let me pass.
Would you have preferred I left him there?
[Zeus groans]
Why are you here?
Hera's gone too far.
I'm here to join you if you'll have me.
[laughs]
She offered them your beloved sea.
Didn't she?
[chuckles] [Zeus] Yes.
Do you know where the cauldron is?
No.
But there is a caravan of maroon wagons
in their rear guard, heavily protected.
If I had to guess, I'd say it's there.
[groans]
[epic music]
We must attack.
[Zeus] We will keep Hera's gaze
locked on us.
Blind her to everything else
that moves about the battlefield.
With Hera distracted, we can send someone
around their lines to find the cauldron.
[Zeus] We have to eliminate the giants.
It's our only hope.
I'll go.
I'll find it.
[Heron] You are the swiftest of the gods.
The one Hera would most expect.
I'll go.
You?
He's right.
She'd never expect something like this.
We can't risk the fate
of the war to a mortal.
[Zeus] He's not a mortal.
He's my son.
[uplifting music]
[chirping]
[heroic music]
[neighs]
[epic choral music continues]
[Evios] Oh.
That'll come in handy.
[Apollo] Wait.
Hephaestus wanted you to have these.
[gentle music]
[Apollo] From one bastard to another.
[loud thudding]
They're here.
[thud]
[thudding and rumbling]
[howling]
[ominous music]
[rumbles]
[neighing]
[thudding continues]
[ominous music]
[quivers]
Do you remember the demons
Alexia was chasing?
They were there to meet up with us.
We found the remains of a giant
and we sold it to them.
Well…
if you still want redemption,
today is your lucky day.
[tense music]
We'll make our stand here.
[Zeus] And rain down fire on them
until there is nothing left but ash.
No army has ever taken Olympus.
And no army will!
[crackling]
Fire! [echoing]
[thunderous choral music]
[swooshes]
[demons scream]
-[horses neigh]
-[demon groans]
[rumbles]
-[horses neigh]
-[demon groans]
[explodes]
-[crackles]
-[Zeus groans]
It's time, Heron.
[whispering] This is how
you show the world who you really are.
[explosions]
[retches]
[loud thud]
Bet that's the first time
in your life you felt small.
[both groan]
[uplifting choral music]
He made it.
Now!
Shorten your range!
[god] Fire!
[brays]
[Zeus groans]
[grunts]
[explodes]
[Zeus] Heron, they've reached Olympus.
Hurry.
[somber music]
-[whirs]
-[both groan]
[both scream]
[screaming]
[intense choral music continues]
[heroic choral music]
[blast]
[crackles]
[loud thud]
[panting]
[groans]
[thwacks]
[Zeus grunts]
[heroic music]
[Heron] It's not here.
[Alexia] Heron, look!
-[crows cawing]
-Do you hear that?
Hear what?
I think I know where the cauldron is.
[whistles]
[gentle howl]
[epic choral music]
[crows cawing]
[gentle howl]
[Zeus groans]
They'll… they'll betray you.
Don't let them destroy Olympus.
You should have thought of that
before you slept with that whore.
[crows cawing]
[panting]
[gasps]
[crackling]
Argh!
[grunts]
[groans]
[Zeus] Now. Quickly, Heron.
[epic choral music]
[growls]
Go!
[exhales deeply]
[panting]
[Zeus] Hera.
Stop this before it's too late.
Hera, please.
You did this to yourself!
[gasps]
No!
[Hera screams]
Hera!
[screaming in pain]
[grunting]
[crackles]
[screeches]
[epic heroic music]
[explodes]
[screams, groans]
[crackles]
[gasping]
[groans, pants]
[low growl]
[Hera panting]
[Hera groaning]
[howls]
[groaning]
You really must choose sides more wisely.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[loud thudding]
[panting]
[elegiac music]
[gasps]
[uplifting choral music]
[groans]
[screaming]
[explodes]
[gasps]
No.
You should have joined me
when you had the chance.
Aaah!
[somber music]
[inaudible]
[Hera screams]
Aargh!
[Seraphim grunts]
[cawing]
[ominous choral music]
[majestic music]
[groans]
[Poseidon groans]
[epic choral music continues]
There's no one left to stop me.
Ah!
[grunts]
-[groans]
-[grunts]
[intense heroic music]
[both groan]
[grunts]
[roars]
[Alexia groans]
[thuds]
[panting]
-[thuds]
-[groans]
[horse neighs]
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
[Seraphim groans]
[loud thud]
-[grunts]
-[bangs]
[panting]
[Zeus] It's time, Heron.
[pants]
You won't be here forever.
[grunts]
Your anger is unyielding.
You rely on it.
[Zeus] You think it gives you strength.
But you don't know what real strength is.
[screams]
[groans]
[retches]
[ pants]
[Seraphim] Look at what
they've done to us.
They ruined our lives.
[Seraphim] Our mother is dead
because of them.
Join me, brother.
[Heron] So you can rule.
[grunts]
[groaning]
[gasping]
[Zeus] Not all foes can be defeated
by strength or anger.
True power is found when one is calm.
Turn inward.
[Zeus] Enough!
Heron! Let your anger go!
Turn inward.
[groans, gasps]
[Heron panting]
[inaudible]
[Evios] Hey, lovebirds.
Well done.
[panting]
[screaming]
[groans]
[retches]
Aah!
[elegiac music]
[Zeus] Not all demigods
have divine strength
but I believe you do.
Let's find out.
[panting]
[groans]
[Seraphim] I know your heart, brother.
-Run!
-Your rage, your fear.
No!
I felt it, too.
[Seraphim] For the sake of our mother
I will ask you one last time.
You are either with me or against me.
[Heron] If that is what
the choice must be…
I'm against you.
[thunderous choral music]
[thunder rumbling]
[crackles]
[screaming]
[somber, serious music]
[ominous music]
[somber choral music climaxing]
[bangs]
[uplifting music]
[sighs]
[groans softly]
[pensive music]
[hopeful music]
[Hermes] He was very proud of you.
As we all are, brother.
[gentle music]
[Kofi] That will be a good scar.
[hopeful choral music]
[crackles]
[choral music climaxes]
[Seraphim groans]
Huh.
[swooshes]
[ominous music sting]
[dark voice] You've used my bident well.
Who are you?
Hades.
[dark music sting]
[gasping]
It's far worse than you can imagine.
But I can help you.
[Hades] Save you from the fate
that awaits you there.
I just need you to do one thing for me.
Kneel.
[dark choral music]
[screaming]
[closing theme music]